Currently 2-A's "Snow White" Is Showing
#12 "Don't Let Go of the Mic, Even if You Die"
My, what a cute little house.
Small chairs and a small table.
I wonder who lives here.
Their costumes and the set
look much more professional than I expected.
It's even standing room only.
But why is this place so covered in dust?
Will you all help me clean?
Of course, Snow White!
Do you think we can win?
No way.
It's not just a matter of their Snow White.
Their entire cast is on another level.
How much did they rehearse to get this far?
How do you like the show, Makabe Masamune?
Did you find Gasou?
No.
Do you have his replacement?
There aren't any other boys
who could fit in his costume.
Then why did you let the show go on?
Because Aki-sama decided that she
would go on even without a prince!
As you all know, Gasou Kanetsugu
still hasn't been found.
What's going to happen?
Are we canceling?
But we all rehearsed more than anyone else.
But...
The Woodcutter,
the Castle Soldier,
the Queen... everyone.
Wouldn't it frustrate you if
we canceled because of this?
Everyone who isn't busy right
now is looking for the prince.
We just need to keep our hopes up and
continue putting on the best show we can.
That's what we're going
to have everyone watch.
We will now begin Class 2-A's
presentation of "Snow White."
She said that she didn't want to
retreat in the face of the enemy.
Adagaki-san said that?
Good for you.
If we can't find Gasou Kanetsugu
by the end, the play will fail.
Everything will go according to your plan!
Wait—
Masamune-sama!
That's right. I'm not going to cry.
I won't lose. I'll be fine.
I'll live on with my head held high.
We have to let him out.
Huh?
I have to get Master to let Kanetsugu out.
Where are you, Master?
You're up there?!
If that's where you are, how am
I supposed to get a hold of you?!
Are you all right, Masamune-sama?
Did your fever come back?
No, I'm fine.
What's bad right now isn't my
health. It's this situation.
Think... There must be a way.
Some way to remedy this...
A way to let this play stick its landing.
Fujinomiya-san.
Yes?
I have a favor to ask you.
Masamune-sama, that's...
Please!
Please...
I shall go.
Huh? Makabe Masamune?
From Class B? Why?
May I help you, Makabe Masamune-san?
If you've come here just to
laugh at us, please leave—
That's not it!
I know this is crazy.
My head is throbbing, and I feel like I'm
going to pass out from the fever, but...
Hey, if you don't want
to end this unfinished,
please hear me out.
The Princess has died!
Snow White-sama!
And so, Snow White was put
into a coffin by the dwarfs.
I guess they never found Kanetsugu.
Even after we tried so hard...
That's enough. We'll just have
to end the show like this.
Snow White died after eating the apple.
She won't come back to life.
Actually, this is more realistic.
You can't rely on the prince.
That's what it comes down to.
Is this a dream or an illusion?
To think I'd find a coffin
in a place like this...
Hey, wait...
That's the prince, right?
But the actor's...
Fujinomiya-san!
Where's Masamune-kun?
Wh-Why is Masamune-kun in
Class A's "Snow White"?!
Everyone's watching.
Everyone's staring hard.
I'm sweating... Did my fever go up again?
Or is it because of the lights?
But I can't turn back now!
I'll take the stage in Gasou's place.
And I'll take this play to the end.
Wha—
Do you understand what you're saying?
I'm pretty sure I do.
Listen. We are enemies.
You, from Class B, intended to win
this competition as well, didn't you?
So why would you...
I do intend to win. I did intend to win...
But I didn't think the production being put
on right now deserved to be destroyed.
So you're implying that this is
genuinely for the sake of art?
As much as I hate to admit it...
Please don't be alarmed,
good people of the forest.
I understand exactly how you feel.
Just go along with it!
I'm sorry for causing such a stir.
Just shut up and go along with it!
I have one question. What happened here?
Come on, connect! Just keep going!
Keep it going! Connect! Keep
going! Keep going! Connect!
Well, my Prince...
Our Snow White...
...has sadly taken her final breath.
Bravo! They caught on!
Snow White—
What the hell is that man doing?!
A-Are you all right, Prince?
Get a hold of yourself, Prince!
Please stand up.
I'm just tired from my long journey.
My chronic illness...
P-Please don't push yourself
too hard, Prince.
Just how weak is this prince?!
Well, it's no surprise.
Huh?
He's got a cold. His fever's
probably pretty high.
Fever?
I thought he might actually be
trying to ruin the performance.
I don't think he really has
that in him right now.
Please...
Just hold out until the end.
Just a little more....
I can't pass out here.
You must have had a hard journey, my Prince.
Th-Thank you...
Don't forget this later.
Now go and gaze upon the princess's face.
Anyway, I just have the kiss left.
After that, I can crawl into a bed.
I can pass out then.
But for now, kiss! The end!
I just need to say my final line,
kiss her, and it'll be over.
What are you waiting for?
We just have to pretend
to kiss, and it'll be over.
Hurry up and get to it!
What a beautiful princess!
It's as though she's only sleeping.
Kiss her, and it'll be done.
Kiss her, and it'll be done...
What are you doing?!
Yay. Snow White-sama
came back from the dead.
Yay!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
A-And so Snow White lived happily ever after
with the prince and the dwarfs of the forest.
A happy end for one and all.
Karaoke
And so, the Yasaka Festival ended
yesterday without a hitch.
The winner of the popularity poll was
Class 2-A's production of "Snow White."
Class B had to cancel their
performance, so they came in last.
Therefore, the winner of
this match was Class A.
And the Best Hero and Best Heroine awards
went to Makabe Masamune-kun
and Adagaki Aki-sama.
This isn't fair!
You say that, but...
Well, Class A was only able to finish
their play because Masamune-kun
appeared in it without telling us, right?
Masamune-kun went straight to
the nurse's office after that...
And my whole script was completely ruined!
I'm sorry.
Well, when I offered to be
Class B's prince in your place...
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Don't underestimate the
importance of pairings.
It's not like just anyone is good
enough for Kojuurou-kyun!
Wha—
Whatever. It's all in the past.
More importantly, why are so many
people crammed in such a small space?
We were thinking of having
an after-party here.
Oh, so were we.
Now, now. All the other rooms were full,
so this party room was all they had.
Why is the atmosphere so tense?
Oh, I know. Why don't you settle things
from the cultural festival here?
Huh?
Well, we have both classes here.
We'll just settle things with a song battle.
There's no point in competing.
I know exactly how it'll
end before we even start.
And exactly why do you
think we're going to lose?
Right, Kojuurou-kyun?
R-Right...
Fine. We'll accept this challenge.
How about whoever loses has
to pay the entire tab here?
All right. Very well.
We're having a song battle, Masamune-sama.
R-Right...
All right, then...
Who will be the true victor?
The karaoke song battle!
The first one up is...
I, Futaba Tae, will go!
Masamune-kun, could you put
in "Selfish MIRROR HEART"?
Masamune-sama, will you put in the request?
Uh, sure.
One sec...
Uh... Huh? Hm...
Do you want me to do it for you?
Thanks, Kojuurou.
I haven't used this type of device before.
It's in, Class Rep.
Okay! Let's do this!
The first one up from
Class B is Futaba Tae-san!
Selfish
Lyrics: Masaki Erika
Composition: Katou Yuusuke
The song she chose is "Selfish MIRROR HEART!"
Selfish MIRROR HEART!
Look at my upside-down eyes!
Points
Volume
Control
Technique
Emotion
Rhythm
Comments: You were mostly keeping with
the rhythm. Let's keep trying harder.
Calories Burned:
How's that?
That was my true power!
You're very good, Futaba-san.
Nah, it was nothing.
I'll go next.
Aki-sama, we're counting on you.
Snow Flower
This isn't weakness or me being needy
I just love you
That's what I thought from my heart
Points
Volume
Control
Technique
Emotion
Rhythm
Comments: You're able to sing for a long time on the
correct pitch. Hearing your singing is very soothing.
Calories Burned:
You're amazing, Aki-chan.
It wasn't my best, but
I guess it is what it is.
Not your best, my ass...
Fast
Interrupt Reservation
Original Song
Key Reservation
Reserve
Now, then... I guess I'm up next.
Do your best, Fujinomiya-san.
I shall.
Goodbye, The One I Love Most
Lyrics: Kojima Izumi
Composition: Kojima Izumi
Oh, I love this song. It's
so sad, but such a good song.
Yes. It's a breakup song that
perfectly fits how I feel right now.
You brute.
Goodbye, the one I love most
Wha—
What the hell is this situation?!
Goodbye, the one I love most
I still love you
Are you plotting something again?
If I'm inferring correctly,
I'm so disappointed, I'm so sad
Makabe Masamune is not
accustomed to karaoke.
Now that you mention it,
he does seem a bit tense.
This is our chance, Kikune-chan.
If Aki-sama sees just how
pathetic and pitiful he is,
Please just come back
she'll become disillusioned.
She'll completely despise Makabe.
You're so smart, Sonoka!
Yoshino, aren't you next?
Walk Over Amagi Pass
Lyrics: Yoshioka Osamu
Composition: Gen Tetsuya
So stoic!
Her lingering scent that you couldn't hide
How about this?
I-I wonder what it is...
She's on pitch,
Had eventually stuck to you
but I've never heard someone sing
"Walk Over Amagi Pass" this way.
In a way, she's definitely the only one.
Rather than have someone take you from me
Makabe-kun, did you decide on a song?
No, not yet...
One sec...
May I just kill you instead?
Ugh, it's throbbing...
Maybe I'll just go home.
You're not allowed to run away.
If you're trying to keep Aki-sama
from seeing how pathetic you are,
it's too late for that.
Wh-What are you...
Well, you're the hot normie Makabe-kun.
I'm sure karaoke is easy-peasy for you.
We want to hear you sing.
I'm sure we'll be moved.
Of course—
What are you doing?
Aki-sama?!
It's not fair for the hosts to put further
pressure on one of the participants, is it?
We're sorry.
Come on, hurry back to the
room. Everyone's waiting.
Okay...
Th-Thanks...
Did she just back me up?
She even came out of the room...
I don't need you to thank me.
Or not!
Come on, let's go. It's almost your turn.
R-Right...
Th-This is the opening song from Hadapure!
Smile de Hadapure!
Lyrics: yuiko
Composition: Ramseeni
Wh-Who put this in without saying anything?
I did.
I thought it wouldn't hurt to put it in while
Masamune-sama was away from his seat.
I-I see.
Damned Commando Catgirl! When did she...
Could you hand me that mic there?
I-I know that!
She looks super pissed.
Would you like to sing along with me?
It is a duet, after all.
I guess I don't have a choice.
Smile, everyone!
I'm always Hadapure!
Hey, look this way
Come on, don't be shy
It's no fun unless you keep your head up
We're definitely
Yeah! Positive!
Keep your dreams big and bold
I want to become
As sparkly as a jewel
Just kidding!
Pure heart
I'm so excited!
I can't be stopped yet
We'll find it, no matter what!
Go forth, Hadapure! Pure, so pure!
We won't lose in cuteness
Let the flower of courage bloom,
and let all the excitement out
I'm Hadapure!
We want to send kindness to your skin
Let's get excited again
So tomorrow
Our smiles will be pure-pure, too
So excited! Hadapure!
Aki-sama!
Wow, that was amazing!
Hadapure sure brings back memories. I loved it.
So cool!
The best Hadapure is, of course,
the original, Whitening-chan.
You must be joking.
Surely you mean Sunscreen-sama.
I guess we'll never see eye to eye.
They're hopeless.
You're the final act, Masamune-kun.
That's right!
What're you gonna sing?
Then...
Lyrics: ChouCho
Composition: AstroNoteS
Listen to the cries of my soul!
Hello. Will you be placing an order?
Huh?
Someone...
Please help...
Hello? Hello?
Hello?!
Man, that was embarrassing.
What did you guys think?
I burned fifteen calories.
Unable to Score
We were unable to score this.
Calories Burned:
That's about the same as fifty sit-ups.
Wow, I didn't know you could burn
so many calories by doing karaoke.
Maybe I'll add it as a new
part of my workout regimen.
I wonder why everyone went home, though.
Right, Adagaki-san?
By the way, where's Koiwai-san?
She's out shopping.
I ended up using more energy
than necessary because of you.
Because of me?
Anyway, why did you stay behind?
You should have gone
home with everyone else.
I'll go home after Koiwai-san comes back.
What?
It's dangerous for a girl to be
out here by herself at this hour.
Though I'm sure that even
if some guy came up to you,
you'd chase him away.
If you know that...
What happened last time
might happen again, too.
Do whatever you want.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, you know, you never
did thank me for that.
Huh? You're bringing that up now?
I properly apologized for that,
and you did it all on your own, anyway.
That's right. You always
do whatever you want.
Like at the cultural festival...
What do you want me to do?
Huh?
I'm asking you what you want me to do.
You know, to thank you...
Whoa, where's this coming
from, Cruel Princess?
Why are you being so sincere?
No, this must be a trap.
Any minute now, she'll bare her fangs.
H-Hurry up and tell me.
Th-Then, um... How about a kiss?
How about you kiss me this time?
D-Did I go too far?
Did I ask for too much?
All right.
Huh? She said yes so easily?!
Th-Then will you close your eyes?
Uh, um...
It's embarrassing, so
hurry up and close them.
O-Okay!
Are you ready?
Make sure you don't open your eyes.
If you open them, I'll be mad.
Wh-What am I supposed to do next?
Actually, how do I look right now?
Maybe I look really stupid...
No, damn it. Straighten up!
Sweet... And hot...
Wait, what?!
That's plenty for you.
And I gave you half of my precious
food, so you should be thankful.
So good.
Go on, eat it before it gets cold.
I-It is good.
Right?
Let's go home, Yoshino.
You never follow through, Pig's Foot.
M-Master?
A little bit more and you might
have gotten your revenge.
Huh?!
Why didn't you go for it instead of waiting?
Y-You mean...
You're so stupid, Pig's Foot.
What are you doing, Makabe Masamune?!
But I've only just begun.
Adagaki Aki...
Next time, I will make you
fall in love with me...
Notice of Class Trip
Destination: Paris, France
And then dump you.